1888pressrelease.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy - 1888 PressRelease

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY USING ANY OF THE SERVICES, YOU REPRESENT THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTAND THE AGREEMENT, WHICH INCLUDES THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY ALL ITS TERMS. TERMS NOT DEFINED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY HAVE THE MEANING DESCRIBED IN THE TERMS OF USE.**

**Sharing of Information**  
1888PressRelease.com is a Newswire dissemination service which distributes press releases on behalf of our clients. If you submit a press release for distribution through our network, your press release will be transmitted in its entirety. This will include any personal information that is contained in your media contact information. When you submit your press release through our system you agree with our policy and understand that your contact information will be disseminated.

**Disclaimer**  
1888PressRelease.com disclaims any content found in news releases. Issuers of news releases are solely responsible for the accuracy of their content.

**Updates**  
1888PressRelease.com from time to time may periodically send out newsletters to our registered members regarding features updates, and updates on company owned websites, services and products. The newsletter may include a sponsor.

**Information Collection**  
1888PressRelease.com does not collect any personally identifiable information unless provided by you, and we will not share, rent or sell any of your personally identifiable information provided by you. The only time information is shared is when a customer of company submits their contact information during distribution of their news release.

**Policy Changes**  
Company may change this Privacy Policy at any time at its sole discretion. Notice of material changes to this Policy will be posted on 1888PressRelease's Website. We will not reduce your rights under our Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most future changes to be minor.

**Contact Information**  
Click here to contact us.
